Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Printed Music, Loose Sheets:
  - DREAM ON, words and music by Ted Mossman, Buddy Kaye, and Goetz Van Eyck, undated (Box 28)
  - DREAMS FOR SALE, words and music by Gene Dickel, Harry Kogen and Clark Dennis, undated (Box 28)
  - A DREAM, J. C. Bartlett, undated (Box 28)
  - DRINK TO ME ONLY WITH THINE EYES, Roger Quilter, undated (Box 28)
  - A DUDELE, Leo Low, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - DUE ARIE, Antonion Vivaldi, undated (Box 28)
  - DUETTO, music transcribed from Mendelssohn, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - THE DYING NIGHTINGALE, Normal Dello Joio, undated (Box 28)
  - THE EAGLE AND ME, music by Harold Arlen, lyrics by E. Y. Harburg, undated (Box 28)
  - EASTER LILIES, words by Elfrida Norden, music by Ken Walton., undated (Box 28)
  - EAST SIDE OF HEAVEN, lyrics by Johnny Burke, music by James V. Monaco, undated (Box 28)
  - EBB TIDE, lyrics by Carl Sigman, music by Robert Maxwell, undated (Box 28)
  - ECTASY OF SPRING, Rachmanioff, undated (Box 28)
  - EILI EILI, Josef Rosenblatt, undated (Box 28)
  - THE ELMS, Leo Kopp, undated (Box 28)
  - ENCORE, words and music by Anita Gray Little, undated (Box 28)
  - ENJOY YOURSELF, lyrics by Herb Magidson, music by Carl Sigman, undated (Box 28)
  - ENOUGH, music by Esther Cooper, undated (Box 28)
  - ERES TU, Miguel Sandoval, undated (Box 28)
  - AN ERISKAT LOVE LILT, English adaptation by Marjory Kennedy-Fraser, undated (Box 28)
  - ESCUCHA, TU, music and Spanish lyrics by Coltilde Arias, undated (Box 28)
  - ESPANA CANI, Pacual Marquina, 3 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - EVELINA, music by Harold Arlen, lyrics by E. Y. Harburg, undated (Box 28)
  - EVENING PRAYER, E. Humperdinck, undated (Box 28)
  - EVEN THOUGH THE WORLD KEEPS CHANGING, David Daimond, undated (Box 28)
  - EVERYBODY SAYS DON'T, music and lyrics by Stephen Sondheim, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - EV'RY NOW AND THEN, lyrics and music by Will Lorin, undated (Box 28)
  - EV'RY STREET'S A BOULEVARD, words by Bob Hilliard, music by Jule Styne, undated (Box 28)
  - EV'RY SUNDAY AFTERNOON, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 28)
  - EVERYTHING I HAVE IS YOURS, lyrics by Harold Adamson, melody by Burton Lane, undated (Box 28)
  - EV'RYTHING I LOVE, music and lyrics by Cole Porter, undated (Box 28)
  - EV'RYTHING I WANT, music and lyrics by Jack Lawrence and Stan Freeman, undated (Box 28)
  - EVERYTHING YOU SAID CAME TRUE, words and music by Cliff Friend and Dave Franklin, undated (Box 28)
  - EV'RY TIME, words and music by Hugh Martin and Ralph Blane, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - EV'RY TIME WE SAY GOODBYE, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 28)
  - EYES THAT LOVE, lyrics by Harry B. Smith, music by Sigmund Romberg, undated (Box 28)
  - THE FAIRY TAILOR SONG, words by Rose Fyleman, music by Michael Head, undated (Box 28)
  - FAITH, music and lyrics by Jack Lawrence and Stan Freeman, undated (Box 28)
  - FAITH IN SPRING, Franz Schubert, undated (Box 28)
  - FALLING IN LOVE WITH LOVE, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 3 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - FALLING LEAVES, music by Henry Lefkowitch, undated (Box 28)
  - FALTERING DUSK, A. Walter Kramer, undated (Box 28)
  - FANTASY, words by Luvia Willard, music by Rudolf Schramm, undated (Box 28)
  - FAREWELL MY LOVE, words by Lou Holzer, music by Harry Kogen and Henry Busse, undated (Box 28)
  - FAREWELL SONG, music by Douglas Moore, lyrics by John Latouche, undated (Box 28)
  - FARGES MICH NIT, words by Jacob Jacobs, music by Abraham Ellstein, undated (Box 28)
  - FAR INTO THE NIGHT, lyrics by Marty Symes, music by Lou Singer, undated (Box 28)
  - FATE, words by Joe Abend, music by Allan Small, undated (Box 28)
  - F.D.R. JONES, words and music by Harold J. Rome, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - FEELING GOOD, words and music by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley, undated (Box 28)
  - FERRY-BOAT SERENADE, lyrics by Harold Adamson, music by E. Di Lazzaro, undated (Box 28)
  - THE FICKLE FINGER OF FATE, music and lyrics by Jack Lawrence and Stan Freeman, undated (Box 28)
  - FIND ME A PRIMITIVE MAN, words and music by Cole Porter, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - THE FIREMAN'S BRIDE, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, music by Sigmund Romberg, undated (Box 28)
  - THE FIRST PSALM, by Gene Bone and Howard Fenton, undated (Box 28)
  - THE FISHERMAN'S LIFE, words and music by Martin and Kalmanoff, undated (Box 28)
  - FLAHOOLEY, words by E. Y. Harburg, music by Sammy Fain, undated (Box 28)
  - FLAME, words by Eddie Mathews, music by Dick Winson, undated (Box 28)
  - FLEDERNANS FANTASY, by Frank LaForge, undated (Box 28)
  - FLOWER OF DAWN, lyrics by Eddie De Lange, music by Russ Morgan and Carl La Magna, undated (Box 28)
  - FLUTTERING BIRDS, by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 28)
  - FOG, Roy Harris, undated (Box 28)
  - A FOGGY DAY, words by Ira Gershwin, music by George Gershwin, undated (Box 28)
  - FOOLIN' OURSELVES, words and music by Billy Barnes, undated (Box 28)
  - FOREVER BEGINS TODAY, words and music by Mort Green and Ralph Norris, undated (Box 28)
  - FOUR SONGS, Jean Barger, undated (Box 28)
  - FRAGMENTS, lyrics by Florence B. Rowland, music by Luther L. Rowland, undated (Box 28)
  - FRIENDSHIP, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 28)
  - FROM ME TO THEE, Erich J. Wolff, undated (Box 28)
  - FROM ONE LOVE TO ANOTHER, lyrics by Albert Gamse, music by Ernesto Lecuona, undated (Box 28)
  - FROM THIS MOMENT ON, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 28)
  - THE FUNNY OLD HILLS, words and music by Leo Robin and Ralph Rainger, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GAMBLER'S WIFE, by John Jacob Niles, undated (Box 28)
  - GARDENIAS, by Harold Lawrence, Barry Niesen, and Jay Milton, undated (Box 28)
  - GENTLE DOVE, Jan Meyerowitz, 4 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - GESU BAMBINO, by Pietro A. Yon, undated (Box 28)
  - GET A LOAD OF THAT CRAZY WALK, words by Don Raye, music by Gene De Paul, undated (Box 28)
  - GET OUT OF TOWN, words and music by Cole Porter, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - GETTING TO KNOW YOU, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 28)
  - A GHOST OF A CHANCE, lyrics by Bing Crosby and Ned Washington, music by Victor Young, undated (Box 28)
  - GIANNINA MIA, by Otto Hauerbach and Rudolf Friml, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - GIGI, words by Alan Jay Lerner, music by Frederick Loewe, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - GIMME SOME, lyrics by Lee Adams, music by Charles Strouse, undated (Box 28)
  - GIPSY LIFE, by Clara Edwards, undated (Box 28)
  - GIPSY MELODIES, Frank LeForge, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GIRL FRIEND, words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GIRL NEXT DOOR, words and music by Hugh Martin and Ralph Blane, undated (Box 28)
  - GIVE ME A NIGHT IN JUNE, by Cliff Friend, undated (Box 28)
  - GIVING AND TAKING, Georges Bizet, undated (Box 28)
  - GLAD TO BE UNHAPPY, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 28)
  - GOD BLESS THE HUMAN ELBOW, music by March Sandrich, Jr., lyrics by Sidney Michaels, undated (Box 28)
  - GOD IS MY FRIEND, lyrics and music by J. Fred Coots, undated (Box 28)
  - GOLDEN DAYS, music by Leroy Shield, words by Bruce Kamman, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GOLDEN LADY, Normand Lockwood, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GOLDEN RULE, Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 28)
  - GOODBYE TO ROME, words by Carl Sigman, music by R. Rascel, undated (Box 28)
  - GOOD FOR NOTHIN', lyrics by Eddie De Lange, music by Jimmy Van Heusen, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - GOOD MORNING, words by Arthur Freed, music by Nacio Herb Brown, undated (Box 28)
  - GOODNIGHT, IRENE, words and music by Huddie Ledbetter and John Lomax, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GOOD SHEPARD, Beardsley Van De Water, undated (Box 28)
  - GOTTA GET SOME SHURT-EYE, lyrics by Johnny Mercer, music by Walter Donaldson, undated (Box 28)
  - GO 'WAY FROM MY WINDOW, John Jacob Niles, undated (Box 28)
  - GRANADA, Ernesto Lecuona, undated (Box 28)
  - GRANADA, I. Albeniz, undated (Box 28)
  - GRANADA, Agustin Lara, attachment, undated (Box 28)
  - GRANT AVENUE, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 28)
  - GREAT DAY, words by William Rose and Edward Eliscu, music by Vincent Youmans, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GREATEST MISTAKE OF MY LIFE, by James Netson, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GREAT INDOORS, lyrics and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 28)
  - GREAT MEMORIES, Elinor Remick Warren, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GREEN DOG, by Herbert Kingsley, undated (Box 28)
  - GREENSLEEVES, R. Vaughan Williams, undated (Box 28)
  - GROWING PAINS, words by Dorothy Fields, music by Arthur Schwartz, 2 copies, undated (Box 28)
  - THE GYPSY BARON, music by Johann Strauss, undated (Box 28)
  - GALWAY BAY, Dr. Arthur Colahan, undated (Box 28)
  - HACE UN ANO, Valdes Veal, undated (Box 29)
  - HALF THE BATTLE, music by Mark Sandrich, Jr., lyrics by Sidney Michaels, undated (Box 29)
  - HAMAVDIL, by Joseph Rumshisky, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HANG YOUR HEART ON A HICKORY LIMB, lyrics by Johnny Burke, music by James V. Monaco, undated (Box 29)
  - HAPPY FEET, words by Jack Yellen, music by Milton Ager, undated (Box 29)
  - HAPPY HABIT, music by Arthur Schwartz, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, undated (Box 29)
  - HAPPY TALK, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 29)
  - HATIKVAH, by Henry Leftowitch, 3 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HATIKOVOK, by L. N. Imber, undated (Box 29)
  - HAUNTED HEART, lyrics and music by Howard Dietz and Arthur Schartz, undated (Box 29)
  - HAVAH NAGILAH, Henry Lefkowitch, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HAVE A HEART, words and music by Mickey Rooney and Sidney Miller, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN SO SOON, words by Edward Heyman and Sam Coslow, music by Abner Silver, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HAVE YOU MET MISS JONES?, words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HAVIVA 'LE, music by Abraham Ellstein, words by Aliza Greenblatt, undated (Box 29)
  - HEART AND SOUL, words by Frank Loesser, music by Hoagy Carmichael, undated (Box 29)
  - A HEART THAT'S FREE, lyrics by Thomas T. Railey, music by Alfred G. Robyn, undated (Box 29)
  - HEAVEN CAN WAIT, lyrics by Eddie De Lange, music by Jimmy Van Heusen, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HEAVEN'S LITTLE ACRE, lyrics by Jimmy Eaton, music by Robert Stolz, undated (Box 29)
  - HEFFLE CUCKOO FAIR, words by Rudyard Kipling, music by Martin Shaw, undated (Box 29)
  - HELLO, PATSY FAGAN, words and music by Michael Donovan, undated (Box 29)
  - HELLO, YOUNG LOVERS, music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, undated (Box 29)
  - HE LOOKS AT HER AND THEN HE GOES HA-HA-HA-HA-HA, words by Billy Rose, music by Ray Henderson, undated (Box 29)
  - HERE, O MY LORD, words by Horatius Bonar, music by Alfred M. Greenfield, undated (Box 29)
  - HERE’S TO YOUR ILLUSIONS, words by E. Y. Harburg, music by Sammy Fain, undated (Box 29)
  - HER GOWN, lyrics by Clarence Walters, music by Henry E. Sachs, undated (Box 29)
  - HE'S A RIGHT GUY, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - HE'S GOT THE WHOLE WORLD IN HIS HANDS, adapted by Geoff Love, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HE'S THE MAN I ADORE, words and music by Dana Suesse, undated (Box 29)
  - HEVEYNU SHALOM A'LEYCHEM, music and lyrics by Shlomo Ben-Chaim, undated (Box 29)
  - HE WANTED TO GO AND HE WENT, book and lyrics by G.M. Wright and Robert B. Smith, music by Victor Herbert, undated (Box 29)
  - HE WAS TOO GOOD TO ME, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 29)
  - HIGH IN SIERRA, music and Spanish lyrics by Ernesto Lecuona, undated (Box 29)
  - HIST! HIST!, by Dr. S. Arnold, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HI-YO, SILVER!, by Vaughn De Leath and Jack Erickson, undated (Box 29)
  - HOME, by Peter Van Steeden and Harry and Jeff Clarkson, undated (Box 29)
  - HOMEWORK, lyrics and music by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 29)
  - HONEY LAMB, lyrics by John W. Bratton, music by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 29)
  - HONEY WON'T YOU COME BACK TO ME?, words by Clarence Wisor, music by Bob Carleton, undated (Box 29)
  - HOUSE BLESSING, music by Frank LaForge, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW CAN YOU BUY KILLARNEY?, by Morrison Kennedy and Grundland Steels, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW CAN THEY TELL THAT OI'M IRISH?, written and composed by C. W. Murphy, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW DID HE LOOK?, words by Gladys Shelley, music by Abner Silver, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW'DJA LIKE TO LOVE ME, words by Frank Loesser, music by Burton Lane, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW DO I LOVE THEE?, Norman Dello Joio, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW DO I KNOW IT'S REAL, words and music by Dan Shapiro, Jerry Seelen, and Lester Lee, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW DO YOU SPEAK TO AN ANGEL?, music by Jule Styne, lyrics by Bob Hilliard, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW FAIR THIS SPOT!, S. Rachmaninoff, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW HIGH THE MOON, words by Nancy Hamilton, music by Morgan Lewis, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW LAUGHABLE IT IS, music by Mark Sandrich, Jr., lyrics by Sidney Michaels, undated (Box 29)
  - HOW STRANGE, lyrics by Gus Kahn, music adapted by Herbert Stothart and Earl Brent, undated (Box 29)
  - HURDY-GURDY, music by Philip Warner, undated (Box 29)
  - HURRY HOME, words and music by Joseph Meyer, Buddy Bernier, Bob Emmerich, undated (Box 29)
  - I ALWAYS KNEW, Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - I AM AN AMERICAN, words and music by Ira Schuster, Paul Cunningham, and Leonard Whitcup, undated (Box 29)
  - I AM ASHAMED THAT WOMEN ARE SO SIMPLE, music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - I AM PRAYER, text by Allen J. Neiburg, music by Paul Weirick, undated (Box 29)
  - I BEGGED HER, lyrics by Sammy Cahn, music by Jule Styne, undated (Box 29)
  - I BELIEVE, words and music by Ervin Drake, Irvin Graham, Jimmy Shirl, and Al Stillman, undated (Box 29)
  - I CAN DO WONDERS WITH YOU, lyrics by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 29)
  - I CAN'T BE TALKIN' OF LOVE, by John Duke, undated (Box 29)
  - I CAN'T DO THE SUM, lyrics by Glen MacDonough, music by Victor Herbert, undated (Box 29)
  - I CAN'T FACE THE MUSIC, lyrics by Ted Koehler, music by Rube Bloom, undated (Box 29)
  - I CAN'T GET YOU OUT OF MY MIND, lyrics by Irving Talor, music by Vic Mizzy, undated (Box 29)
  - I CONCENTRATE ON YOU, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - I COULD WRITE A BOOK, words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 29)
  - I COULDN'T SLEEP A WINK LAST NIGHT, words by Harold Adamson, music by Jimmy McHugh, undated (Box 29)
  - I CRIED FOR YOU, by Arthur Freed, Gus Arnheim, and Abe Lyman, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I DON’T MIND BEING ALL ALONE, by Clarence Gaskill, Jimmy McHugh, and Irving Mills, undated (Box 29)
  - I DON'T THINK I'LL FALL IN LOVE TODAY, words by Ira Gershwin, music by George Gershwin, 3 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I DON'T WANT TO CRY ANYMORE, words and music by Victor Schertzinger, undated (Box 29)
  - I'D RATHER HAVE A PAL THAN A GAL ANYTIME, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Josef Myrow, undated (Box 29)
  - I'D RATHER LISTEN TO YOUR EYES, music by Harry Warren, lyrics by Al Dubin, undated (Box 29)
  - I DREAM TOO MUCH, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, music by Jerome Kern, undated (Box 29)
  - IF, words by Robert Hargreaves and Stanley J. Damerell, music by Tolahard Evans, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I FALL IN LOVE WITH YOU EVERY DAY, words by Frank Loesser, music by Manning Sherwin, undated (Box 29)
  - I FALL IN LOVE TOO EASILY, lyrics by Sammy Cahn, music by Jule Styne, undated (Box 29)
  - I FIND MY LOVE, Morris Mamorsky, undated (Box 29)
  - IF FLOWERS COULD SPEAK, by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I CAN HELP SOMEBODY, music by A. Bazel Androzzo, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I DIDN'T CARE, words and music by Jack Lawrence, undated (Box 29)
  - HE IS THE TYPE, lyrics by Anne Caldwell, music by Jerome Kern, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I FORGET YOU, words and music by Irving Caesar, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I HADN'T MET YOU, by Sam M. Lewis, Abel Baer, and Cliff Hess, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I KNEW THEN, words and music by Dick Hurgens and Eddy Howard, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I LOVE YOU A MOUNTAIN, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Josef Myrow, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I RULED THE WORLD, words by Leslie Bricusse, music by Cyril Ornadel, attachment, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I SHOULD LOSE YOU, words and music by Leo Robin and Ralph Rainger, undated (Box 29)
  - IF I WERE ON THE STAGE, lyrics by Henry Blossom, music by Victor Herbert, undated (Box 29)
  - IF YOU ARE BUT A DREAM, by Moe Jaffe, Jack Fulton, and Nat Bonx, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - IF YOU'RE IRISH, COME INTO THE PARLOR, words and music by Shaun Glenville and Frank Miller, undated (Box 29)
  - IF YOU ARE THERE, words by Henrik Ege, music by Michael North, undated (Box 29)
  - IF YOU FEEL LIKE SINGING, SING, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Harry Warren, undated (Box 29)
  - IF YOU HAVEN'T GOT A SWEETHEART, words by Dorothy Fields, music by Arthur Schwartz, undated (Box 29)
  - IF YOU SEE STARS IN MY EYES, words and music by Maxine Hawley and Hal Brandis, xerox copy, undated (Box 29)
  - I GET A KICK OUT OF YOU, music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - I GET ALONG WITH YOU VERY WELL, words and music by Hoagy Carmichael, undated (Box 29)
  - I GO FOR THAT, words by Frank Loesser, music by Matt Malneck, undated (Box 29)
  - I GOT A ONE TRACK MIND, music by Morton Gould, lyrics by Betty Comden, undated (Box 29)
  - I HAD A BALL, music and lyrics and Jack Lawrence and Stan Freeman, undated (Box 29)
  - I HAPPEN TO BE IN LOVE, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - I HATE MEN, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - I HAVE DREAMED, words by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I HAVE EYES, words and music by Leo Robin and Ralph Rainger, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I KNOW A GARDEN, words and music by Arthur H. Gutman, undated (Box 29)
  - I KNOW WHERE I'M GOIN', arranged and edited by Herbert Hughes, undated (Box 29)
  - IL BACIO, Luigi Arditi, 5 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I LET A SONG GO OUT OF MY HEART, words by Iriving Mills, Henry Nemo, and John Redmond, music by Duke Ellington, undated (Box 29)
  - I LIKE A MAN AROUND THE HOUSE, music by Baldwin Bergersen and Albert Selden, lyrics by Phyllis McGinley and Billings Browns, undated (Box 29)
  - I LIKE TO RECOGNIZE THE TUNE, words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, 3 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'LL BUY YOU A STAR, music by Arthur Schwartz, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'LL FOLLOW MY SECRET HEART, words and music by Noel Coward, attachment, undated (Box 29)
  - I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN, words and music by Noel Coward, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'LL STILL BE LOVING YOU, words by Albert Stillman, music by Corinne Hiter, undated (Box 29)
  - I LONG TO BELONG TO YOU, lyrics by John Redmond, music by Mary Schaeffer, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I LOVE LIFE, words by Irwin M. Cassel, music by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 29)
  - I LOVE THE LADIES, music by Mark Sandrich, Jr., lyrics by Sidney Michaels, undated (Box 29)
  - I LOVE YOU, Cole Porter, 3 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I LOVE YOU MUCH TOO MUCH, by Alexander Olshanetsky, undated (Box 29)
  - I LOVE YOU SO, words by Adrian Ross, arranged by H.M. Higgs, undated (Box 29)
  - I LOVE YOU TRULY, words and music by Carrie Jacobs-Bond, undated (Box 29)
  - IMAGINE ME WITHOUT YOU, words by Ira B. Gershwin, music by Lewis E. Gensler, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M ALL SMILES, lyrics by Herbert Martin, music by Michael Leonard, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M A LUCKY DEVIL, words by Peter Tinturin, music by Al Jacobs, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M ALWAYS IN THE MOOD FOR YOU, words by Benny Davis, music by J. Fred Coots, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M A POACHED EGG, words by Ira Gershwin, music by George Gershwin, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M BASHFUL, words by Bob Merrill, music by Al Schofield, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M GLAD I'M NOT YOUNG ANYMORE, words by Alan Jay Lerner, music by Frederick Loewe, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M GONNA WASH THAT MAN RIGHT OUTTA MY HAIR, WORDS BY Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Richard Rodgers, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M HAPPY ABOUT THE WHOLE THING, lyrics by Johnny Mercer, music by Harry Warren, undated (Box 29)
  - I MIGHT BE IN YOUR ONCE IN A WHILE, music by Victor Herbert, lyrics by Robert B. Smith, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M IN LOVE AGAIN, words and music by Cole Porter, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M IN THE MOOD FOR LOVE, lyrics and melody by Jimmy McHugh and Dorothy Fields, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M LIKE A NEW BROOM, words by Dorothy Fields, music by Arthur Schwartz, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M MAD ABOUT THE GIRL NEXT DOOR, lyrics by Mack Gordon, music by Josef Myrow, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M MADLY IN LOVE WITH YOU, words by Benny Davis, music by J. Fred Coots, undated (Box 29)
  - THE IMPOSSIBLE DREAM, lyrics by Joe Darion, music by Mitch Leigh, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M PRAYING TO SAINT CHRISTOPHER, lyrics by Harry MacPherson, music by Albert Von Tilzer, undated (Box 29)
  - IMPROVISO, Francisco Mignone, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M PUTTING ALL MY EGGS IN ONE BASKET, lyrics and music by Irving Berlin, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M PUTTING ME IN YOUR HANDS, lyrics by Martin Charnin, music by Colin Romoff, undated (Box 29)
  - I'M WISHING, words by Larry Morey, music by Frank Churchill, undated (Box 29)
  - IN A MOMENT OF WEAKNESS, lyrics by Johnny Mercer, music by Harry Warren, undated (Box 29)
  - IN A SENTIMENTAL MOOD, music by Duke Ellington, lyrics by Irving Mills and Manny Kurtz, undated (Box 29)
  - IN-CHI-CHI-CASTENANGO, words by Henry Myers, music by Jay Gorney, undated (Box 29)
  - INDIAN LOVE CALL, words by Otto Harchah and Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Rudolf Friml, undated (Box 29)
  - IN EGERN ON THE TEGERN SEE, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Jerome Kern, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - IN JUNE, words by Helen Field Watson, music by Raymond Lloyd Adams, undated (Box 29)
  - IN MOTHER'S ARMS, words and music by L. Stewart Barr, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - INTERLUDE, words by George O'Neill, music by Andre Kostelanetz, undated (Box 29)
  - IN THE MIDDLE OF A DREAM, lyrics by Al Stillman, music by Einar Swan and Tommy Dorsey, undated (Box 29)
  - IN THE STILL OF THE NIGHT, words and music by Cole Porter, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - INVITATION TO THE WALTZ, arranged by Janet Lind and A. Gibilaro, undated (Box 29)
  - I PASSED BY YOUR WINDOW, words by Helen Taylor, music by May H. Brahe, undated (Box 29)
  - I PROMISE YOU, words and music by Samuel Lerner, Ben Oakland, and Alice Faye, undated (Box 29)
  - I REMEMBER IT WELL, words by Alan Jay Lerner, music by Frederick Loewe, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)
  - I REMEMBER, music Max Gneiss, poem by Thomas Hood, undated (Box 29)
  - IRENE, lyrics by Joseph McCarthy, music by Harry Tierney, undated (Box 29)
  - IRISH LULLABY, by Mary Howe, undated (Box 29)
  - I SEE THE MOON AT NOON, lyrics by David Greggory, music by John Gerald, undated (Box 29)
  - I SEE YOUR FACE BEFORE ME, words by Howard Dietz, music by Arthur Schwartz, undated (Box 29)
  - I SHALL KNOW, lyrics by Helen Jerome, music by Mana-Zucca, undated (Box 29)
  - I SING, words by Eric Von Der Goltz, music by Gustav Klemm, undated (Box 29)
  - IS IT POSSIBLE?, lyrics by Al Dubin, music by Jimmy McHugh, undated (Box 29)
  - I SING MY SONG TO YOU, words and music by Martin Kalmanoff, undated (Box 29)
  - IS THAT NICE?, lyrics and music by George Dennis, undated (Box 29)
  - I STILL LOVE TO KISS YOU GOODNIGHT, lyrics by Walter Bullock, music by Harold Spina, undated (Box 29)
  - IT AIN'T NECESSARILY SO, music by George Gershwin, lyrics by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, undated (Box 29)
  - Italian STREET SONG, lyrics by Rida Johnson Young, music by Victor Herbert, 2 copies, undated (Box 29)